[Anzu] Come on, Hijiri,
I already told you.
Don't bother asking me out.
But Tsuchiya said,
that meant I should ask you out.
Tsuchiya!
Sincerest apologies.
[Hijiri] I looked into
some places normal folk enjoy.
I'd appreciate it
if you'd show some gratitude
that you are able to date me.
[mimics choking]
[sighs]
I'm not a realistic
potential romantic partner for you, am I?
What are you saying?
I'll have you know,
every woman in the world sees me
as a potential romantic partner for them.
All right. I'm about to beat you at drums.
No whining if I hit you by accident.
Sorry, that one's not interesting.
Why don't we play this one over here?
Oh.
That plushie toy I wanted
last time is still there.
Rio took all of our prizes home
that night.
-What?
-Hmm?
I'd still plan a better date.
There's no way
you know her as well as I do.
Your disrespectful cousin.
-All right, I'll buy everything in there.
-[snaps fingers]
Will my paycheck cover it, Tsuchiya?
Allow me to check with the manager.
[Anzu] Just play the game, please!
Why bother with that part of it?
I really don't understand.
[Anzu] Hmm.
Hey, I know. Let's hit the photo booth.
-Whoa!
-Mr. Tsuchiya, come on!
You want me in it?
[Anzu] Yup.
[cheerful music]
[Anzu] Hurry, Mr. Tsuchiya!
[Tsuchiya] Yes, miss.
-[Tsuchiya grunts]
-[automated voice] Give me a hot pose!
-Oh. Right there, the camera.
-Hmm.
-[automated voice] Three, two, one.
-[exclaims]
[camera clicks]
SP TRIO
[Anzu] Somehow we do always end up
having fun together.
-[Yukana] Miss Anzu Hoshino.
-Hmm?
Nice to meet you.
How are you? My name's Yukana Kishi.
Tsukasa, he lives with you
at your place, isn't that right?
Um…
We've been together,
for, well, I'd say for quite a while now.
[insects chirruping]
[theme music]
#11 JUST TELL ME IF YOU DON'T LIKE IT
Mr. Hijiri.
[Hijiri] What is it?
Well, I thought I was seeing things,
so I kept quiet at first.
But I could sense someone's eye
on us all day today.
[gasps]
[Tsuchiya] We parted ways
with Miss Hoshino at the station,
but I must say I'm concerned.
I can check up on her.
[Anzu] So you're Kazuki's, uh, girlfriend?
Yes, I am.
But everybody who's close to us is
against it for some reason,
so I'm never allowed to see him anymore.
[Yukana] It's terrible, isn't it?
Tearing lovers apart that way?
[Anzu] I don't know.
I just don't see Kazuki
being with someone like her.
[Yukana] His sister
is truly an evil person,
the complete opposite of my sweet Tsukasa.
[Anzu] I just don't know.
Something feels off.
[foreboding music]
[uneasy sigh]
I've been searching frantically
because no one would tell me
where he moved.
And I found him thanks to social media.
WITH CHOYO. LOOK AT THE HOTTIE
IN THE BACKGROUND.
[Anzu] What?
[Tsukasa gasps]
[thuds]
[Yukana gasps]
How come… you're…
[Yukana] Tsukasa!
[Anzu] Whoa, this is bad.
[Tsukasa gasps anxiously]
I'm sorry, but he's busy.
So please, time for you to leave.
[pensive music]
[exhales deeply]
[breathing heavily]
[Anzu] Man,
Kazuki's really sweating over there.
Hmm.
[sighs in relief]
[Anzu] She's gone now, Kazuki.
[Tsukasa] How did she,
how did she approach you?
Well, she called out my name
when I was walking home.
[Anzu] Then she told me
that she was your girlfriend.
[retches]
[Anzu] Kazuki!
-[retching]
-[Anzu gasps]
[Tsukasa in hoarse voice]
And, did you, did you believe her?
Mm-mm.
-No, I didn't. Something felt off.
-[Tsukasa grunts]
[exhales sharply]
[groans weakly]
She's, uh…
[Tsukasa] She's my stalker.
What?
[eerie music]
[Tsukasa] I'm starting
to feel a lot better now.
[Anzu] I'll get you
something to drink. Uh?
Stay with me a little longer.
[Anzu] Jeez, his hands are super cold.
Sorry.
[Anzu] It's okay.
I'm really sorry too.
I shouldn't have even talked to her.
It's not your fault.
Knowing how she is,
she already had your address.
[Tsukasa] Anyway.
You knew. You could sense it.
[sighs softly]
Well, I did say I would tell you
why I was living alone.
You shouldn't feel pressured
to talk about it.
I want to, Hoshino.
[gasps]
[Tsukasa] Here's how it happened.
[Yukana grunts]
-You know that book I wanted?
-Oh yeah.
-Well, dude, I really--
-Huh?
[hurried footsteps]
[Tsukasa] Are you okay?
Here.
[gasps]
[Yukana] Thank you very much.
[Tsukasa] All I did was give her the bag.
[rain pattering]
-Hey, remember that book?
-Yeah, did you get it?
-[boy 1] I did, man, for nearly after…
-Morning.
Oh. Good morning.
Morning.
[gasps]
[Tsukasa in weak voice]
Hello.
That chick's here for you,
like, every day.
Mm-hm.
Hey, she must like you a lot, my dude.
[Tsukasa] Nah,
I'm sure it's not like that.
[boy 1] Man, it must be nice
to be so good-looking.
[doorbell dings]
[delivery man] Delivery.
TO: TSUKASA KAZUKI
For me?
[foreboding music]
Hmm.
Hmm?
And it totally freaked me out.
-That makes sense.
-Hey, Mom, about this shirt…
Oh, is that a new one?
Did Arisa get it for you?
What? No, I didn't get it for him.
Huh?
[sighs]
[boy 2] No, dude,
it was just like I thought.
[boy 1] He's confiscating everything.
-So your brother had…
-Oh, really? That's crazy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That dude would take
all my stuff without asking.
[Yukana] Morning.
-That shirt looks so good on you.
-[Tsukasa gasps]
What?
[doorbell dings]
[breathes heavily]
[doorbell dinging]
[cutlery clinking]
[Tsukasa's mom] So disturbing.
Someone created multiple accounts
for different websites
using my name without my permission.
Thank goodness
the purchases weren't billed to you.
But this is still serious.
I think we should speak to the police.
[Tsukasa's dad] There's no reason
to involve the police. Shame on you!
Tsukasa.
You're making these purchases
using your mom's name, aren't you?
-No--
-Do you really think
Tsukasa would ever do that?
-Don't talk to your father that way.
-Huh…
[Arisa sighs]
[Tsukasa's mom] Anyway, let's just
return the packages unopened for now.
[Yukana] Tsukasa,
you like the gifts I send?
[Tsukasa] I knew it. You sent everything.
Hmm.
[Tsukasa] Why are you doing this?
Oh. I'm sorry,
I didn't mean to bother you.
I should have asked
what kind of clothes you like first.
[Tsukasa] No, that's not what I mean.
You made a bunch of accounts
using my mom's name.
Well I, I haven't really met
your family yet, so,
are you worried about what they may think?
Embarrassed if they found out about us?
[Tsukasa] What are you…
[gasps]
So…
What clothes do you like, then?
[Yukana] Just tell me, Tsukasa.
[scared gasps, breathing nervously]
Please, just don't send me anything else
ever again. Just leave me alone.
[melancholy music]
-[boy 2] Hey, so check it out.
-What's up?
Remember what my big brother did?
-No.
-[boy 2] Well, I ratted him out to my mom.
-[boy 2 laughs]
-[boy 1] It's pretty crazy, right?
[boy 2] No way, dude.
Hey, isn't that the girl who waits
for you, like, every single morning?
What? Uh, I don't know.
-Hmm?
-Hmm.
[rain pattering]
[breathing nervously]
[boy 2] See you later, dude.
Have fun tonight.
-[student 1] Yay!
-[student 2] We have a test tomorrow.
[scared gasp]
[eerie music]
[Tsukasa gasps]
[moaning]
[suspenseful music]
[grunting]
[Yukana] Oh, Tsukasa,
you're so shy, aren't you?
I understand that you don't want anyone
close to you to know about us.
Since I still get to see you every day,
I can suffer
through us not being able to speak.
My sweet Tsukasa.
Seems everyone else…
is in the way.
GIRLS MY AGE ARE ANNOYING AND CREEPY
ALL GUYS ARE IMMATURE.
I WISH THEY LEFT ME ALONE.
[boy 2] Isn't that the chick who's always
waiting for you on our way to school?
[girl 1] Excuse me,
you're dating older women now?
SECOND ACCOUNT OF A STUDENT.
MAINLY COMPLAINTS.
[boy 3] Dude, how are you
gonna talk trash about us online?
[girl 2] She's obviously
trying to get with me.
He can't just diss me like that.
[boy 4] What the hell is that post, dude?
[girl 3] Tsukasa, you're legit the worst.
[boy 2] I can't believe
you're so two-faced, man!
-[smacks]
-[Tsukasa's mom and Arisa gasp]
[Arisa] Hey!
[Tsukasa's dad]
You have some woman following you
who put a wire and a camera on you?
Disgraceful!
It's not Tsukasa's fault, Dad!
He is the victim here.
[Tsukasa's dad] This happened
because you lead her on.
You're not sincere with people.
-[Yukana] Tsukasa.
-[gasps]
This is awful.
[breathing nervously]
All everyone wants to do was
pull us apart.
And we're so deeply in love
with each other--
-[slams]
-[Tsukasa gasps]
-[Arisa pants]
-[Yukana groans]
Go away!
We have a restraining order against you!
So unless you wanna spend
the rest of your life in jail,
don't come near my brother ever again!
[Yukana shudders]
[Tsukasa] I'm off to school.
[Tsukasa sighs]
[breathing nervously]
[twisted chuckle]
[laughing]
[distorted chatter]
[Tsukasa grunts]
[sobbing]
[sighs]
Tsukasa.
[Tsukasa] And after all that,
I couldn't even go to school.
[Tsukasa] If only I hadn't stopped
to pick up her bag.
And if… I regretted that moment
again and again in my head,
I still do.
My homeroom teacher,
my mom, and Arisa helped me.
And I moved away.
And started living alone
so no one could find my address.
I got to a place
where I could live a normal life,
but I still feel sick when people stare,
and when girls approach me.
I'm just a spineless loser
so all I can do is be cold,
and put up walls to protect myself.
Even when my dad came at me,
I was too weak to defend myself.
All of it happened
because I don't make genuine relationships
and let people in.
None of my classmates believed
a word that I said,
and all of it is my fault.
[sobs]
Kazuki, stop me if you hate it.
-[Anzu] 'Cause I'm gonna hug you now.
-[gasps]
[surprised gasp]
[melancholy music]
None of this is any of your fault.
-I'm so mad.
-[Tsukasa gasps]
[Anzu] If only
we had become friends sooner.
I would have believed you,
even when nobody else did.
[sobs]
I feel the same way.
I wish I had met you sooner too.
[Arisa] I went ahead
and contacted the police.
We're gonna have to be guarded
for a while.
I'm sorry you're dealing with this.
[Tsukasa] It's because I'm weak.
It's so embarrassing.
[Anzu] Hey, that's not true.
Don't worry. I'm right here.
[soft guitar music]
[Arisa sighs]
[Arisa] Social media
can be really problematic.
I can't believe how fast she found you.
Hmm.
Well, I'll stay over on the days
that I don't have to work.
You don't have to do that.
I'm sure you're busy as well.
[sighs]
Listen.
I know you're mature for your age,
but you're still just a kid.
[Arisa] So, let people help you
when you need it.
[slams]
[Yukana's mom]
Would you let it go with this kid?
[frustrated sigh]
You're causing too much trouble now.
We can't just keep running
to your uncle every time you do this.
Jeez, I don't believe any of this
would have happened
if this damn guy didn't lead you on…
Don't say that about Tsukasa!
[Yukana] When I was getting bullied
at work every day,
Tsukasa was such a sweetheart to me.
Every day, he would come visit.
And we talked about,
well, anything all day.
[Yukana's mom exhales heavily]
[Yukana's mom]
How could he do this to you?
I wanna take him to court.
[door opens]
[Yukana] We were only
seeing each other, nothing more.
[Yukana sobs]
It's not anybody else's business but ours.
And now yet another girl
is getting too close to my Tsukasa!
[exhales sharply]
She's in the way.
[manager] Ah, Hoshino,
you can go after you finish cleaning that.
Okay.
What's up? You don't normally look upset.
Huh? Um…
Uh…
Yeah…
[Hijiri] We don't have
any customers right now,
so I'm happy to lend you an ear.
But don't get excited, I'm not worried
about you or anything silly like that.
Will you chill out
with the hot and cold, Hijiri?
[Anzu] He texted a few times yesterday
to check on me.
In his own way, he's making sure I'm okay.
ARE YOU OKAY?
IF YOU ARE OKAY, IT'S FINE
[Anzu] I was just thinking about
what I might be able to do
to, uh, help out a friend of mine.
[soft piano music]
[Hijiri] Well,
as long as you're near them,
I'm sure everything will be all right.
Huh?
Wait, what?
So that's what you think about me, huh?
Please don't touch me.
Aw, shoot. Hoshino already left, huh?
[manager] Well, she forgot her phone here.
If we run, we can catch her.
I'll just send Tsuchiya.
-[snaps fingers]
-How can I help, sir?
[manager]
I've been wondering all this time,
what country are you the prince of,
Mr. Koganei?
[Saki] Hi there. Is Anzu in the back?
-No, she just left.
-[door closes]
What? She sent a text asking me
to come pick her up with my brother.
-[Saki's brother grunts]
-[Saki] Uh…
Oh, shoot! Did I forget my phone?
[groans in frustration]
What a drag. Oh?
[suspenseful music]
Hey.
[nervous gasp]
[punk 1] We're gonna need you
to come over here with us.
[Anzu] Huh? What? Who are you?
[punk 1] I'm sorry, girl,
but we were told to make sure
you can't be out in public.
-[Anzu groaning]
-[thuds]
[yelps]
[punk 1] Huh?
-[bone cracks]
-Huh?
[grunts]
What are you doing? Get away from Anzu.
Uh, Junta…
-Damn it…
-[punk 1 groans]
Who the hell is this brat?
[punk 2 grunts, groans]
-[thuds]
-[Anzu gasps]
Ryuya!
-[groans]
-Tonta, stay out of it!
-You can get kicked off the team!
-[grunting]
[Anzu gasping]
[punks groaning]
Hey, back off!
[surprised gasps]
Pardon, I'm not sure what's going on here,
but I'm afraid I'll have to stop you.
-[groans]
-[bones crack]
Mr. Tsuchiya!
Miss Hoshino, my sincerest apologies.
I'm sorry to intrude.
But I'm here to deliver
something you forgot.
-[grunts]
-[gasps]
[groans]
The hell, man?
[Ryuya clears throat]
Hold up, you guys. Naoki, is that you?
[gasps]
Mr. Takamine!
Wanna tell me what the hell you're doing?
I'm so sorry.
[Naoki] We had no choice.
This crazy chick threatens us.
[foreboding music]
Was she around 20?
Did she have really dark hair,
to about here?
Yeah, that's right.
[gasps]
[Saki's brother] You two ain't getting off
easy for this, you hear?
Right, Shades-y?
I'm sorry. Shades-y, you said?
Oh, brother,
was that supposed to be clever?
Um…
[insects chirruping]
[Anzu] I'm okay, thanks to you guys.
I just can't believe everyone showed up
with such great timing.
[Ryuya] Well, I mean, I did get
that super random text from you.
What? A text?
[Saki] Yeah, and you messaged me
to bring my brother,
-so I didn't know what to expect.
-Hmm?
WANT TO GO TO THE ARCADE AFTER?
[Anzu] Wait.
WHEN DO YOU GET OFF?
I don't remember sending any of these.
I don't think you're safe here.
You should really hurry home
and try to get some rest.
Oh? Yeah, I'll go do that.
Thank you all so much, seriously.
[Arisa] What? I honestly can't believe it.
[Anzu] I know, but thankfully
nothing serious happened.
I should leave. I mean,
after all that, I can't stay here.
[sighs]
-[Anzu] I won't let you.
-[gasps]
-[Anzu] You shouldn't have to suffer…
-Mm.
…just because someone like her is
out there.
Let's figure this out as a team.
[exhales deeply]
[Tsukasa] Thanks.
Bad moods are a big no-no!
This cute boy right here will help you
get into a good one!
Kick rocks. You embody my negativity.
Oh wow, you're hard.
[humming happily]
[Rio] You know, I got you out
of that sticky situation
by sending those texts to everyone
with your phone.
What, it was you? You send the texts?
[Rio] Yes, ma'am.
I set the whole thing up,
so that all of the pawns
would come running to protect you.
Don't you dare call them "pawns"!
[sighs]
Anyway, thank you.
You really saved my life.
First time I'm grateful for you.
An ant's booger's worth.
A microscopic level, oh!
[Anzu] Look, if you're a wizard,
can't you do something about this stalker?
Like, put up a barrier, maybe,
that keeps her from finding Kazuki.
Hmm.
I'm only able to use my magic,
if it contributes
to your romantic relationship somehow.
Here's the thing.
If you do nothing about it,
then you would be exposing me to danger,
am I right?
Whoa…
Well, if it's true you're going
to be exposed to future danger,
[Rio] I'll just have to remove Kazuki
from your potential partner options.
[groans]
[Rio] Gotta eliminate those risky pawns,
am I right?
[Anzu grunts]
Heh?
-[Anzu grunts]
-[Rio] No!
-[squeaks]
-[yells]
I'm done talking
to anyone without a heart.
[Anzu] Get out.
[door closes]
[Rio] Aw, jeez.
Well, now I won't be able
to use my magic again for a while.
-[phone keyboard clicking]
-[door opens]
I can't fall asleep.
[Junta groans]
I'm really thirsty.
Sorry Junta, for putting Hoshino
in all this danger.
Why are you apologizing?
[Junta sighs]
You shouldn't feel responsible
for any of this stuff.
Hmm.
Luckily, Anzu didn't get hurt
this time around.
But I won't let that stalker do this.
I swear, if she threatens Anzu again,
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
If it gets me kicked off the team,
then so be it.
I've made up my mind now,
and I have no regrets.
It's got nothing to do with you.
[Junta] Truth is, the reason
I started playing baseball was…
-What kind of guys do you like, Anzu?
-Hmm?
Hmm…
Someone who's super athletic!
[fighting grunts]
And can beat the boss!
[Junta] Those were her exact words.
[zapping on TV]
[Anzu] Tonta, you got
great hand-eye coordination.
-Would rock at baseball, I bet.
-[gasps]
[Junta] So, I picked up baseball
in middle school.
Because of what Anzu said.
[muffled laughter]
Hey dude, don't laugh.
No, I'm sorry. I'm sure she has no idea
she was so influential, that's all.
Totally. Oh?
Hi.
[chuckles]
[ominous music]
[Hijiri] Has everything been okay
since the night we spoke?
CONBINI MART
Mm-hm.
[Anzu] Haven't had anything happen since.
[Anzu] Kazuki and his sister
are gonna walk me home after work today.
That's good. But if you ever need
Tsuchiya, you can ask any time.
[chuckles]
Well, thank you.
And if the boss was here, he'd say,
[imitates manager]
"In what country are you an oil tycoon?"
[in normal voice]
You know he'd say that, right?
Yeah, he asked me already.
[Hijiri chuckles]
[Hijiri] Anyway, not even a king
nor an emperor
would interest you at all, right?
Huh? Well, yeah.
[chuckles softly]
All right, break's over now.
-Yeah, I'm gonna head home.
-Good night.
-[Yukana] Miss Hoshino.
-Huh?
[Anzu gasps]
[eerie music]
Excuse me. You got a minute?
[Anzu] Kishi. Oh, shoot.
Tsukasa and Arisa are coming to get me.
They'll be here any sec.
I can't let them see her.
What do you want?
[Yukana] I have something for you.
[Anzu gasps in fear]
[blood splats]
A fanfare, please!
And a big congratulations!
Did you fall for my little trick?
I bet now you don't feel like
skipping the ending, right?
In today's world, you can watch
whatever you want at your own convenience.
But don't you think in that process
we've also lost something?
[sighs]
Don't just let things be! Come on!
Let's go on a super-duper happy adventure!
So I can make sure I get paid.
[closing theme music]
♪ Ah, yeah! ♪
♪ Let's go! ♪
♪ Lo-love! ♪
♪ Here we go! ♪
In today's world, you can watch
whatever you want at your own convenience.
But don't you think in that process
we've also lost something?
[sighs]
Don't just let things be! Come on!
Let's go on a super-duper happy adventure!
So I can make sure I get paid.
[closing theme music]
♪ Ah, yeah! ♪
♪ Let's go! ♪
♪ Lo-love! ♪
♪ Here we go! ♪